<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Marriage Point Calculator</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_welcome_">Marriage Point Calculator</string>
    <string name="title_activity_player_selection">Marriage</string>
    <string name="welcome_message">Welcome To Marriage Point Calculator</string>
    <string name="title_activity_test">Test</string>
    <string name="title_activity_score_card">Score Card</string>
    <string name="title_activity_help">Help</string>
     <string name="title_activity_about">About</string>
    <string name="help_text">
        <b>TO CALCULATE POINTS.</b>\n\n
        <b>Initialization</b>\n
        1. Enter number of players(2-5) and press Submit.\n
        2.Enter Name of players(Optional...You can skip this step, Default Name will be used)\n
        3.Press Continue.\n\n
        
        <b>Point Calculation</b>\n
        1. Choose the Winner by clicking on RadioButton (circular) on right of the Player Name.\n
        2. Select the players who have Seen Maal using CheckBox (Rectangular) to the right of Player Name.\n
        3. Enter the Maal obtained by each Player who have seen.\n
        4. Press Calculate to calculate the points obtained by each player.
         Positive point denotes gain by player and negative point denotes loss.\n
        5. Press save button to save the score.\n
        Scorecard will be displayed that will show Points earned in Each Round and Total Points one has obtained.\n
        6. Press BACK softkey to enter score of Next Round.
        7. Repeat all steps to Calculate Points for Each Round.\n\n
        
        <b>Note</b>\n
        1. You can re-calculate the scores before choosing to save if any mistake is done.(e.g. forgot to check someone as seen or wrong value of Maal is entered.)\n
        2. If the App is force closed or process is killed by system, the App will retain score and ask you in beginning if you want to Resume.\n
        3. <b>Hamro keyboard is not supported in the App. Please use other keyboard.</b>\n\n
        
        <b>Preference Setting</b>\n
        1. To set Rate per Points.\nClick on menu->settings->Rate per Points\n\n
        
        2. To set Seen and Unseen penalty.\nClick on menu->setting->Seen Penalty/Unseen Penalty\n\n
        
        3. To change Game Mode.\nClick on menu->setting->Game Type.\n
        
        4. To view Score in Main Screen.\nClick on menu->View Score.
        
        </string>

    <string name="about_text">
       Marriage is a famous card game popular in South Asian Country like Nepal and India.
       The purpose of this App is to help players calculate points.
       It uses Center Collection Algorithm to calculate points.\n
       Features:\n
       1. Supports variable player number(2-5).\n
       2. User defined point rate.\n
       3. User defined seen and unseen penalty.\n
       4. Two modes of Game Playing\n
       		\ti. <b>Traditional</b>\n
       		\t\t Maal of unseen players will also be counted in calculation.\n
       		\tii. <b>Maal Dhus</b>\n
       		\t\t Maal of unseen players will not be counted in calculation.\n
       
       5. Cumulative scores are saved.\n
       6. Score is resumed even if App is force closed.\n\n\n
       If you find any bug in App,Please report it to following email address\n
       Developer: Som Prasad Shrestha © \n
       E-mail: crestasom@gmail.com
       
       
        
        </string>
    
</resources>
